{
    "subject": "resource/Dr._Luke",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Providence,_Rhode_Island",
    "human_readable": "Dr. Luke was born in Providence, Rhode Island.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9498330354690552,
            "question": "Is Dr. Luke a native of Rhode Island?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8259024024009705,
            "question": "Where was Dr. Luke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145422339439392,
            "question": "In which city was Dr. Luke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733880341053009,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Dr. Luke was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.614170253276825,
            "question": "Where did Dr. Luke come from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5253276824951172,
            "question": "What is the full name of Dr. Luke's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.486939936876297,
            "question": "What state is Providence in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47311803698539734,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dr. Luke's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43816840648651123,
            "question": "What country is Rhode Island in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18778006732463837,
            "question": "Is Providence known for anything specific?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dr. Luke was born in Providence, Rhode Island.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8750_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Rhode Island in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8750_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Dr. Luke's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8750_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Providence in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8750_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8750_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple that Dr. Luke was born in Providence, Rhode Island. This can be confirmed by looking at files path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8750/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8750/re-ranker-msmarco/68.txt, which both mention that Dr. Luke was born in Rhode Island, with one specifying Providence as the birthplace."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Dr. Luke was born in Providence, RI on September 26, 1973,\" which supports the statement that Dr. Luke was born in Providence, Rhode Island."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}